I guess we probably should talk about
Iran. Um, look, uh, I'll just I'll just
let me just frame what's going on. So,
at the latest point, we know that the US
has at least 150 planes, uh, near or
over Iran right now. A dozen military
ships in the Middle East. Um, US embassy
in Beirut just evacuated what they
called non-essential personnel.
>> I was going to mention that.
>> Uh, the we have the two carrier groups
are already there. um joint chairman of
the joint chiefs of staff who's
currently uh Dan Kaine or Raisin Kane is
his uh apparently his his his nickname.
Um he's been publicly telling the press
everything's going to be cool if we
decide to go after Iran. There's nothing
that they can do about it. But privately
warning President Trump that there could
be there's a risk of high casualties if
the US does this. I don't know.
>> Did you see Did you see the reason for
that?
>> I was I was going to ask you that. What
is the reason for that? None of our
allies are helping us. Not a single one
of them.
>> Well, why would they? I mean, this is a
this is a gratuitous attack just like
Iraq was.
>> You know, a war of choice is one thing,
but this is gratuitous. You're right.
>> And I mean, there's not even been any
attempt to jin up a uh you know, a casus
ballet, right? Um and then I thought
this part I really wanted to pick your
brain about this part, John. So, um, he
was also privately worried about
depletion of stockpiles. Now, John, you
and I are both in our six, our low 60s.
I've never heard of the US government
being in danger of running out of
munitions before. Uh, I mean, is this
because we gave so much [__] to the
Israelis?
>> To the Israelis? Yes, it is. And we just
haven't had a chance to to to
manufacture and and refill the supply.
So literally we literally not only uh
participated in uh financing and arming
uh a genocide against the people of Gaza
on behalf of Netanyahu and his
bloodthirsty regime. We also imperiled
American national security and our
ability to project power and to protect
ourselves. Is that basically the story?
>> Yeah. We put ourselves in danger.
>> That's [__] insane.
>> Yes, it is. Yes, it is. So, um, look,
>> let me May I interrupt you for one
second,
>> please? I I I gotta say something about
Israel. I've been obsessed with the
clips that Tucker Carlson has been
putting out on social media about his um
about his trip to Israel. You know, he
um
he met with with Mike Huckabe at the
airport. Huckabe wouldn't have him into
the embassy. Uh and and Tucker was, you
know, allowed to enter Israel. He
interviewed the Greek Orthodox patriarch
Theophilos III. He interviewed the uh
Catholic Archbishop of uh of Jerusalem.
Huckabe would not have him in the uh in
the embassy. Huckabe had the traitor
Jonathan Pard into the embassy, but not
Tucker. And then as they were leaving
Israel,
the Israelis grabbed two of Tucker's uh
producers, a man and a woman. The woman
they let go. The man they were asking
him like things like who did you meet
with? What did they say? What questions
did you ask? Let me see your phone. I
want to download your phone. Uh who do
you talk to on a daily basis? What's
Tucker's position on XYZ? And the guy
wouldn't answer any of the questions. So
the Israelis came out and told Tucker,
"Just get on your plane and go. We'll
put him on the plane when we're done
with him." And Tucker's like,
"Absolutely not. You're not kidnapping
my producer." And this kid is like 24
years old, 25 years old, panicked. The
Israelis were intimidating.
Um, and Tucker refused to leave. And
finally, they they kicked him out and
kicked him loose and said, "Okay, the
kid's free to go."
But the Israelis, you know, either we're
at the point now where you're either
with them, and when I say with them, I
mean 1,000% with them or you're an enemy
of of uh of Zionism and you're
anti-Semitic.
And I think that we are just about at a
tipping point where the is where the
Israelis will have done themselves
irreparable damage politically in the
United States. Because there are people
who consider themselves or have always
considered themselves to be, you know,
pro- Israel, if not Zionist, pro-Israel.
>> Mhm.
>> And now it's because they never really
paid very close attention to the issue,
>> right?
>> And now they are.
>> And they don't like what they see.
>> Yeah. John, I think I think we we're
past that point already, do you?
>> I don't see I don't think there's
there's coming any coming back. Um the
Israelis are I mean those n the Apac
lobby in this country is so desperate
and and it reeks you know you following
their socials and following the socials
of their allies in Congress you know you
can just you they're they're scared you
know they they know um you know it's
they are one administration away from
really just not having the same
relationship with the US as they always
had. Um, I don't know how that's going
to look. I don't know if that would be a
Buddha Judge or a or a Newsome or
someone else, but or even a Republican
maybe.
>> You know, a friend of mine said, I'm
sorry to interrupt you. A friend of mine
said something interesting on on social
media yesterday and he said, you know,
we're all up in arms about about
Netanyahu and the way he's manhandling
the US government and and you know,
Donald Trump is falling into into place
and just doing as he's told.
Newsome has said nothing.
>> No.
>> Shapiro has said nothing. Kamla Harris
has said nothing. Bernie Sanders has
said nothing. AOC has said nothing.
Hakeem Jeff has said nothing. The
Democrats are completely implicated.
It's as simple as that.
>> No, I mean that is true. And you know
the progressive base of the Democratic
party, they're watching. They're paying
attention. Well, and did you happen to
see the the afteraction report the that
the DNC
uh wrote? Why did we lose the election
in 2024? Uh it was it was kept from the
American people. Of course, these things
usually are released. This time it was
not released. And finally yesterday,
somebody leaked it. And the reason why
the Democrats lost the election to
Donald Trump is because they would not
take a position on Israel standing up to
the Israelis. And so Democratic voters
stayed home.
>> Yep. That's exactly what happened.
People sat on their hands.
>> Yeah. They they should have voted for uh
Jill Stein in my opinion, but I agree.
>> Um John, last week you said that you
talked to someone who um in a position
to not saying that the attack on Iran, I
mean, I think more it's definitely more
likely than not to happen, right? I
mean, I think at this point we're at,
you know, war fever is at a high pitch.
Today, Monday, today is like kind of
like roughly when we were thinking it
might happen.
>> Yes.
>> Um, do you think it'll you you think it
could be like so
do you think Trump is so theatrical that
he might announce like sort of Greg
Stillson like at the speech tonight, the
missiles are flying, allelujah,
allelujah.
God, you know, I just rewatched that
movie not three weeks ago.
>> The Dead Zone.
>> The Dead Zone. The book was even better
than the movie.
>> The movie's great though.
>> The movie's great.
>> One of Christopher Watkins's best
performances,
>> you know, which which proves that he can
do anything.
>> Yeah.
>> Comedy, drama, he can do anything. Lead
actor, supporting actor, makes no
difference.
>> True.
>> Um,
sure it's possible. But somebody said
something to me yesterday that kind of
bothered me and they said, "You got your
information from somebody in the White
House." And I said, "Yes."
Maybe the White House was using you
knowing that you would say something
publicly
just to see what the public reaction to
it would be.
>> Maybe.
>> And I said, "Yeah, I could have been
used." Sure.
>> I mean, yeah, there's no way to know
that. By by all the most recent
accounts, uh Trump is going to wait for
the next round of talks on Saturday. The
likelihood is that he'll say the talks
failed, the Iranians won't concede, and
then we hit him on the weekend.
>> Well, the but the Iranians can't
concede. I mean, not what we're asking
is just not possible for them to agree
to. So, I mean, I don't think any
Iranian government could.
>> Want to support the show with style? Go
to dprogram.live live and check out our
merch. That's dprogram.live
or check out the description below.
Thanks for watching.
[music]